<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Sent to customers when new documents added as part of any advice after onboarding.</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Portal Documents | Advice | Follow on</name>
    <pageDevName>Portal_Documents_Advice_Follow_on</pageDevName>
    <relatedEntityType>Advice__c</relatedEntityType>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NOVA Wealth - New documents available</subject>
    <textOnly>[ADD CORRECT NAMES AND DELETE THIS PROMPT] 

Hi {CLIENT 1 NAME} &amp; {CLIENT 2 NAME},

Your advice documents are now available in the portal. Here you will find a folder containing the following:

[AMEND LIST BELOW AS NECESSARY AND DELETE THIS PROMPT]

 - A recording of your meeting
 - A copy of the presentation, including important risk warnings and appendices that contain important additional details
 - Personalised illustrations for your recommended NOVA products
 - Relevant [PROVIDER]product brochures
 - Passive Plus portfolio Key Investor Information Documents (KIIDs)[REVIEW IF NECESSARY]

Access your document store &lt; https://portal.novawm.com/documents &gt; using your existing email and password. You can also navigate there from the portal menu.

We will notify you whenever important documents are added to the portal.

Next Steps

[NON-PRESENTED ADVICE ONLY]

It&#39;s really important that you review the details of our advice and confirm whether you are happy to go ahead. A simple reply to this email will suffice.

[ONLY IF ACCEPTANCE IS STILL REQUIRED/ONE CLIENT DIDN’T ATTEND RECORDED MEETING]

{Client 2}, as you didn&#39;t take part in the meeting it is important you review the details of our advice, including watching the meeting recording [DELETE IF NON-PRESENTED], and confirm whether you are happy to go ahead. A simple reply to this email will suffice.

To summarise, our advice is to:

 - [take from summary slide in deck]

[TYE payments only]

Please note this advice needs to be accepted by the 28th of March to meet the tax-year-end deadline, you then have until the 4th of April to make this payment.

If you need anything explained in more detail or have any questions, we will be happy to answer these. You can book a meeting with {PARTNER NAME}.

[ADD HYPERLINK TO THE WORDS &quot;book a meeting with {partner name} AND DELETE THIS PROMPT&quot;]

Kind regards

Amy Farringdon

+44 (020) 7390 0222 &lt; tel:+442073900222 &gt; | amy@novawm.com &lt; mailto:amy@nvoawm.com &gt; | Web &lt; https://novawm.com/ &gt; 

The information in this email is intended solely for the recipient. Access, copying or re-use of information in it by anyone else is unauthorised. If you are not the intended recipient please delete the email, inform the sender by reply, or contact Nova Wealth on +44 (020) 7390 0222 &lt; tel:+442073900222 &gt; . Please note that telephone calls are recorded.

NOVA is a trading name of NOVA Wealth Ltd, which is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (FRN: 778951) and is a limited company registered in England &amp; Wales (10739796) at 20 Farringdon Street, London, EC4A 4AB.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>SFX</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
