<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Sent to customers who are getting migrated to portal documents as part of receiving advice.</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Portal Documents | Migrated | Advice</name>
    <pageDevName>PortalDocumentsMigratedAdvice</pageDevName>
    <relatedEntityType>Advice__c</relatedEntityType>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NOVA Wealth - Your documents are now in the portal!</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {~~~CLIENT 1 NAME~~~} &amp; {~~~CLIENT 2 NAME~~~},

One of the most requested features from customers is the ability to access advice and tax documents directly through our portal instead of Dropbox.

We are pleased to announce that we have developed a secure document section within the portal where you can now access all your documents. This enhancement will improve the security of your documents and streamline your experience by consolidating everything in one place, where you already view your investment performance and update your profile.

How can I access documents in the portal?

Simply log in as usual and access documents from the menu, or use this link to go directly there &lt; https://portal.novawm.com/documents &gt; . In this new section, you can access documents and stream your meeting recordings.

What documents can be accessed in the portal?

All the documents previously available in Dropbox, such as advice meeting recordings, presentations, or any historic tax documents are now accessible in the portal. Access to Dropbox has also now been disabled.

Your recent advice 

We have also created a new folder for your recent advice containing the following:

 - A recording of your meeting
 - A copy of the presentation, including important risk warnings and appendices that contain important additional details
 - Personalised illustrations for your recommended NOVA products
 - Relevant [~~~PROVIDER~~~] product brochures
 - Passive Plus portfolio Key Investor Information Documents (KIIDs)

As before, we will notify you whenever important documents are shared with you.

Next Steps [~~~IF APPLICABLE~~~]

[~~~NON-PRESENTED ADVICE ONLY START~~~]

It&#39;s really important that you review the details of our advice and confirm whether you are happy to go ahead. A simple reply to this email will suffice.

[~~~NON-PRESENTED ADVICE ONLY END~~~]

[~~~ONLY IF ACCEPTANCE IS STILL REQUIRED/ONE CLIENT DIDN’T ATTEND RECORDED MEETING~~~]

{~~~Client(s) required to accept~~~}, as you didn&#39;t take part in the meeting it is important you review the details of our advice, including watching the meeting recording [~~~DELETE IF NON-PRESENTED~~~], and confirm whether you are happy to go ahead. A simple reply to this email will suffice.

To summarise, our advice is to:

 - [take from summary slide in deck]

[~~~TYE payments only~~~]

Please note this advice needs to be accepted by the 28th of March to meet the tax-year-end deadline, you then have until the 4th of April to make this payment.

If you need anything explained in more detail or have any questions, we will be happy to answer these. You can book a meeting with {~~~PARTNER NAME WITH HYPERLINK TO CALENDLY~~~}.

Kind regards

Amy Farringdon

+44 (020) 7390 0222 &lt; tel:+442073900222 &gt; | amy@novawm.com &lt; mailto:amy@nvoawm.com &gt; | Web &lt; https://novawm.com/ &gt; 

The information in this email is intended solely for the recipient. Access, copying or re-use of information in it by anyone else is unauthorised. If you are not the intended recipient please delete the email, inform the sender by reply, or contact Nova Wealth on +44 (020) 7390 0222 &lt; tel:+442073900222 &gt; . Please note that telephone calls are recorded.

NOVA is a trading name of NOVA Wealth Ltd, which is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (FRN: 778951) and is a limited company registered in England &amp; Wales (10739796) at 20 Farringdon Street, London, EC4A 4AB.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>SFX</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
